<resources>
    <string name="PPEL_server">https://debianvm.eecs.wsu.edu</string>
    <string name="Questions_API">/api/questions</string>
    <string name="Responses_API">/api/responses</string>

    <string name="app_name">PPEL</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu">this is a menu string</string>

    <string name="info">\tWelcome to the Voiland College Professional Practice and Experiential Learning online mock
        video interviewing program. Interviewing is the toughest part of a job search.  Many applicants are nervous
        about getting caught off-guard by the questions, missing key words, rambling, and just not selling your skills
        and talents to the interviewer.  \n\n\tWith the PPEL mock interviewing program, you\'ll be able to practice and
        save your recorded answers to typical questions, plus request feedback from Voiland College interviewing experts
        or faculty mentors. Log in and start practicing for online interviews today.</string>

    <string name="help_content">\tThank you for using our app.  The following sections explain the details of
        how to use this application.\n\nNavigation:\n\tThere are two ways to bring up the navigation menu on this app.
        Swiping from left to right across the screen, or pressing the three line icon located in the top left corner of
        the app.\n\nViewing Questions:\n\t  In order to watch an interview question on the questions page simply tap
        the question\'s title bar and the video question will expand and begin playing. Tap the title bar again to collapse
        the question. \n\nRecording Question:\n\t To record a response to a given question just press the record answer button
        that is located beneath each question. You will be taken to the video capture interface where you can press a record
        button to start capturing your response.  the button\'s text will change to \'stop\' to indicate that you are recording.
        Press the button to stop recording.   You can record up to a two minute video.\n\n\t  After recording you will be prompted
        to save or delete the video.  If you delete the video it will be removed from your computer.  If you save it then the
        video will be stored until you decide to delete it. Only one video response can be saved per question.  </string>

    <!-- camera stuff -->
    <string name="permission_request">This sample needs permission for camera and audio recording.</string>
    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>

</resources>
